auto-im.com 2012-10-14

# Auto Internet Marketing » AUTO Internet marketing godlmine » Privacy Policy

Information You Choose to Submit

You can visit our website without telling us who you are or revealing any personal information (which we will refer to in this privacy policy as “Personal Data”) about yourself. To obtain access to certain areas of our website, however, or to receive certain services we provide (e.g., creating a website), you may be required to register with us and, in connection with such registration, to provide certain Personal Data (e.g., your email address). We use such information to provide the service you requested, to monitor internally usage of our website, and to contact you from time to time about us, our website, and our products and services. In addition, if you wish to make a purchase from our website, you are required to register with us and, in connection with such registration, to provide certain Personal Data (e.g., your full name, email address, and billing information). We use such information to fulfill your order and to contact you from time to time about us, our website, and our products and services.

Security

We have implemented reasonable measures to help protect your Personal Data from loss, misuse, or unauthorized access or disclosure. Unfortunately, however, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your Personal Information, we cannot guarantee its security.

Email Communications

We send all newly registered users a welcome email to verify username and password. Established users will occasionally receive and update on new content and developments around auto-im.

Spam.  
Users that do not publish meaningful content, use deceptive means to generate revenue or traffic, or whose primary purpose is affiliate marketing, will be suspended.

Hate Content, Defamation, and Libel.  
Hate speech and other objectionable content that is unlawful, defamatory, and fraudulent. Note that an allegation of defamatory expression, in and of itself, does not establish defamation. The truth or falsehood of a bit of expression is a key element in establishing defamation, and we are not in a position to make that sort of fact-based judgment. That said, if we have reason to believe that a particular statement is defamatory (a court order, for example), we will remove that statement.

Links

Our website may contain links to other websites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of any such other website (whether accessed through an advertisement, service, or content link) and urge you to review such practices prior to submitting any personal information to such websites.

Copyright.  
Using copyrighted material does not constitute infringement in all cases. In general, however, users should be careful when using copyrighted content without the permission of those who created it. It is our policy to respond to notices of alleged infringement that comply with the Digital Millennium Copyright Act (“DMCA”).  
And we are not responsible for any copyright material that is on our web site. There is many users that post on our web site. Here on this web site you can find only links that lead to other web sites and nothing else regarding copyrighted materials. If you have some complains about some copyright materials send us mail on copyright(@)auto-im (dot) com

Changes

We may update this privacy policy from time to time. If under any such update we make any material change to the way in which we treat your Personal Data or Usage Data, we will inform you of such change via email or by posting a notice on relevant areas of our website. Any updated version of this privacy policy will be effective as of the date set forth therein.
